[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did Scarlett Johansson make her film debut?", "correct_answer": "1994", "incorrect_answers": ["1988", "1998", "1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aunt Abby and Aunt Martha from Arsenic and Old Lace want Teddy to help them dispose of the dead bodies. What do they tell him about the gentleman they kill?", "correct_answer": "They were yellow fever victims.", "incorrect_answers": ["They were spies, so they had to silence them.", "They were prisoners who tried to escape and were shot.", "They died of natural causes."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Rocky IV, Rockys wife, Adrian, didnt join him the first time he flew to Russia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to scientific classifications, to which kingdom do fungi belong?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["To both the animal and the plant kingdom", "The animal kingdom", "The plant kingdom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert Altman was born on February 20th, 1925 in Kansas City, Missouri. What was the occupation of his father B.C. (Bernard Clement)?", "correct_answer": "an insurance salesman", "incorrect_answers": ["a policeman", "a real estate agent", "a pilot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is true about Charles Furnas?", "correct_answer": "He was the first passenger on an airplane.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was the designer of the Wright Brothers first plane.", "He was the pilot of the first jet fighter.", "During World War I, he became the first man to shoot down a plane during a war."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What  Dirty Dancing character delivered the line, Go back to your playpen...Baby.?", "correct_answer": "Penny", "incorrect_answers": ["Neil", "Johnny", "Lisa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Say Anything, while Lloyd and Diane are walking home after their first date, Lloyd points out what item for Diane to walk around?", "correct_answer": "Pile of broken glass", "incorrect_answers": ["Large stick", "Pile of dog poop", "Puddle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other interesting name is used commonly to refer to the Purple frog, an amphibian endemic to the Western Ghats in India?", "correct_answer": "Pignose Frog", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicken frog", "All of these", "Mole frog"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The concept of spinning animation, the drawing of still pictures on an object that show motion when the object is revolved, dates back to at least this  many years ago.", "correct_answer": "5,000 years", "incorrect_answers": ["10,000 years", "250 years", "500 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Academy Award did the 2007 movie Pirates of the Caribbean: At Worlds End win?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Academy Award for Best Visual Effects", "Academy Award for Best Makeup", "Academy Award for Best Director"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other name is commonly used to refer to the Colorado River in North America?", "correct_answer": "Red River", "incorrect_answers": ["Black River", "Yellow River", "Blue River"]}]